indonesiamatters.com 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

Our webservers collect non-personally identifiable data (your IP address, how often you visit our site, which pages you visit, etc.) each time you visit IndonesiaMatters.com and any of its hosted subdomains. We use this information to make the site better to use and simpler.

We will only collect personally identifiable data (your name, email address, phone number, etc) on forms _you_ complete. These are voluntary. This information might be used to contact you. _You_ are in complete control of what personally identifiable information you give us.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience 
  * To improve our website

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law.

**Third party links**

Sometimes, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.indonesiamatters.com/terms-of-use/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us from the [About page](http://www.indonesiamatters.com/contact-us/).
